Guide to the Browning Photograph Collection 1918-1952 (bulk, 1920-1938) PR 9
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Photographs
  - Occupations
    Occupations includes informal portraits of unidentified people engaging in their work. Many of the occupations represented are at the lower end of the economic scale, and are obviously people suffering from the affects of the Depression. Included are shoe shiners, newspaper vendors and carriers, a street cleaner and a variety of peddlers. Also included is one unidentified violinist.
    - Baker, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 44)
    - Butcher, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 44)
    - Florists (Ninth Ave. street flower market, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 45)
    - Newspaper vendors and carriers (7), undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 46)
    - Organ grinder, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 47)
    - Painter, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 47)
    - Peddlers (49), undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 48-49)
    - Porters (4), undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 50)
    - Sandwich board advertiser, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 50)
    - Shoe shiners (4), undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 51)
    - Street cleaner, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 52)
    - Valet, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 52)
    - Violinist, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 52)
  - Office Buildings
    Office Buildings is the largest subseries, and includes much of Browning's commissioned work. Most photographs show off newly constructed buildings, and some include construction progress photographs, with the Chrysler Building, the Empire State Building, the Daily News Building, the Cities Services Building, the New York Life Insurance Building, and Salmon Tower particularly well represented. This subseries includes photographs of the work of a great variety of architects of the period including William Van Alen, Raymond Hood, Joseph Urban, and George B. Post & Sons, among others.
    - 137 East 57th St. (14), undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 53)
    - 1400 Broadway, clock, undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 54)
    - 1450 Broadway, entrance and clock, undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 55)
    - Chanin Building, 122 East 42nd St., undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 56)
    - Chrysler Building, 405 Lexington Ave., including construction views (22), undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 57)
    - Cities Service Building, 70 Pine St., including construction (30), undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 58-59)
    - Daily News Building, 220 East 42nd St. (13), undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 60)
    - Downtown Athletic Club, 19 West St. (4), undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 61)
    - Empire State Building, 350 Fifth Ave. -- Construction (17), [1929-1931] (Offsite-box 8, Folder 62)
    - Empire State Building -- Exteriors (27), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 63)
    - Empire State Building -- Interiors (21), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 64)
    - Empire State Building -- Photomontages (4), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 65)
    - Empire State Buiding -- Views on and from Observation Deck (6), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 66)
    - Flatiron Building [Fuller Building], 175 Fifth Ave. (2), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 66)
      See also: Box 10, Folder 93
    - Fuller Building, 41 East 57th St. (3), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 68)
    - Goelet Building, 608 Fifth Ave. (3), undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 69)
    - Hearst Magazine Building, 951-959 Eighth Ave., undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 70)
    - Linden Building, East 42nd St., interiors (8), undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 71)
    - Maritime Exchange Building, 80 Broad St. (4), [1930-1932] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 72)
    - McGraw-Hill Building, 330 West 42nd St. (4), undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 73)
    - New York Life Insurance Building, 51 Madison Ave., some with Madison Square, interiors and exteriors (43), [1929] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 74-75)
    - New York Telephone Company, 140 West St., undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 76)
    - 2 Park Ave., undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 77)
    - Rockefeller Center buildings; most are construction scenes, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 78-79)
    - Salmon Tower, 500 Fifth Ave., including construction (14), [1930-1931] (Offsite-box 10, Folder 80)
    - St. Paul Building, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 81)
    - Schwarzenbach-Huber Building, 468 Fourth Ave. (2), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 82)
    - Silver House (4), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 83)
    - Squibb Building, 745 Fifth Ave., interiors and exteriors (9), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 84)
    - Starrett-Lehigh Building, 601-625 West 26th St., includes construction, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 85)
    - 24 West St., undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 86)
    - Woolworth Building, 233 Broadway, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 87)
  - Parks and Squares
    Parks and Squares consists of a variety of views of a variety of public spaces, with Central Park, including Grand Army Plaza and Columbus Circle being represented by the most photographs. Bryant Park, situated adjacent to the New York Public Library is also well documented; included are views of the 1932 replica of Federal Hall under construction in the park.
    - Battery Park (3), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 88)
    - Bowling Green (3), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 89)
    - Bryant Park, many including the New York Public Library and replica of Federal Hall under construction (13), 1932, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 90)
    - Central Park, with Grand Army Plaza and Columbus Circle, 1925, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 91)
    - Gramercy Park, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 92)
    - Madison Square Park, many include Flatiron Building (9), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 93)
    - Riverside Park, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 94)
    - Union Square (2), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 94)
    - Washington Square Park and Washington Arch (6), undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 95)
  - Photomontages
    Photomontages contains the busy compilations Browning developed primarily for his print advertising clients. Most incorporate many images on a particular theme, such as shop windows, transportation, clocks, restaurants, grand buildings, or industry. Many images included in the photomontages can be found as individual prints elsewhere in the collection.
    - Buildings (21), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 96)
    - Business and advertising (14), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 97)
    - Industry and equipment (15), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 98)
    - Sports and recreation (9), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 99)
    - Miscellaneous (25), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 100)
  - Police Stations
    Police Stations includes both interior and exterior views of suburban police stations in East Rockaway, Lindenhurst, and Valley Stream, New York. Included are views of jail cells, offices and police vehicles.
    - East Rockaway Police Station, interiors and exteriors (9), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 101)
    - Lindenhurst (NY) Police Station, interiors and exteriors (6), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 102)
    - Valley Stream (NY) Police Station, interiors and exteriors (7), undated (Offsite-box 11, Folder 103)
  - Portraits
    Portraits includes a Time magazine cover bearing a portrait of New York Governor Herbert H. Lehman by Irving Browning, a group of portraits of renowned anthropologist Margaret Mead, and many unidentified portraits.
    - Lehman, Herbert H. (1878-1963), Time magazine cover portrait by Irving Browning, Vol. XXIV, No. 27, 1934 Dec. 31 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 104)
    - Mead, Margaret (1901-1978) (6), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 105)
    - Unidentified, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 106)
  - Public Buildings and Institutions
    Public Buildings and Institutions includes a variety of major recognizable Manhattan institutions and government buildings such as the Municipal Building, City Hall, the New York Public Library, and the American Museum of Natural History.
    - American Museum of Natural History (2), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 107)
    - City Hall, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 108)
    - Columbia University, Low Library (2), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 109)
    - Federal Hall (2), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 110)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 111)
    - Municipal Building, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 112)
    - New York Public Library, includes aerial view (10), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 113)
      See also: Night Views
    - New York State Supreme Court Building (2), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 114)
    - U.S. Post Office [roof only, seen from St. Paul's Chapel], undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 115)
  - Rain Views
    Rain Views include a variety of locations seen during rain storms or clouds, especially St. Patrick's Cathedral, the Empire State Building through fog, and 42nd Street.
    - 42nd St. (3), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 116)
    - Broadway, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 116)
    - Empire State Building in fog (2), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 116)
    - Herald Square, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 116)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral (2), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 116)
    - Unidentified street scenes (4), undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 116)
  - Residences
    Residences include interiors and exteriors of mostly unidentified residences, especially in the suburbs of New York City. Identified residences include the interior of Fanny Brices's home, the residence of movie mogul Marcus Loew in Glen Cove ("Pembroke"), and houses in the Arbor Close and Forest Close developments in Queens.
    - Arbor Close and Forest Close Developments, Forest Hills, Queens, interiors and exteriors (9), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 117)
    - Brice, Fanny, residence, West 76th St., interiors (21), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 118)
    - Fieldston, Bronx, residences, unidentified (3), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 119)
    - Loew, Marcus residence, "Pembroke," Glen Cove, NY, interiors, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 120)
    - New Jersey residences, unidentified (Teaneck and Palisades) (4), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 121)
    - Pelham, NY, residences, unidentified, interior and exterior (4), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 122)
    - Roscoe, NY residence, unidentified (3), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 123)
    - Scarsdale, NY, residences, unidentified, interiors (3), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 124)
    - Unidentified exteriors (6), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 125)
    - Unidentified interiors (24), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 126)
  - Restaurants
    Restaurants includes many lunch counters and inexpensive chain restaurants, such as Foltis Fischer and Wil-low Restaurant. A photograph of Blake's Doughnut Parlor in Bryant Park features hand-painted Depression-related signs in the window.
    - Astor Hotel Restaurant, interior, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Blake's Doughnut Parlor, Bryant Park [hand-painted Depression-related signs in window], undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Chatham Walk, East 48th St. (9), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Foltis Fischer, 200 East 42nd St., [with Elevated Railroad](3), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Madeira House, 94 Park Ave., undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Prospect House (Tudor City) Dining Room, interiors, East 42nd St. and First Ave. (3), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Rainbow Room, Rockefeller Center, interiors (7), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - St. Regis Restaurant, 1570 Broadway, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 127)
    - Wil-low Restaurant (2), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
  - Roofs and Roof Gardens
    Roofs and Roof Gardens includes views of rooftop patios and gardens as well as clothes hung to dry on apartment building roofs. A view of a man mowing the lawn on the roof of a Park Avenue penthouse, a series of photographs of an unidentified woman lounging with her dogs while being served drinks by a servant on the roof of a private residence, and photographs of residents enjoying the roof of the London Terrace (decorated to look like an ocean liner deck) allow a glimpse of the lifestyle of wealthier New Yorkers.
    - London Terrace Roof (10), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 128)
      See also: Box 1, Folder 6
    - Municipal Building [gathering in tent on roof], undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 128)
    - Miscellaneous (24), undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 128)
  - Ships, Boats and Ferries
    Ships, Boats, and Ferries includes views of a variety of ferries, ferry terminals and ships in New York harbors and rivers. Well represented are Coney Island and Staten Island ferries, as well as the S.S. Leviathon. A few photographs depict a Chagres River ferry in Panama. Several photographs included in this subseries depict the Sailors' Snug Harbor home on Staten Island. Also included are a large number of mostly unidentified photographs depicting ships, boats, sailors, and shipping activity.
    - Ferries
      - Chagres River Ferry (Panama) (2), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 129)
      - Coney Island Ferries (12), 1928, [1930] (Offsite-box 14, Folder 129)
      - Dyckman Ferry, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 129)
      - Roscoe, New York Ferry Bell, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 129)
      - Staten Island Ferries (8), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 129)
      - Weehawken Ferries and Ferry Terminal, [1929], undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 129)
      - Miscellaneous ferry views (7), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 130)
    - Named Ships and Boats
      - Aquatania, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 131)
      - Benjamin F. Packard (3), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 131)
      - Buccaneer, with the Success in foreground, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 131)
      - Dalzellea (tug boat, with other identified tugs), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 131)
      - S.S. Habana, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 131)
      - S.S. Leviathon (19), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 132)
      - London Corporation, with oil kegs on pier, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 133)
      - New Rochelle (tug boat), undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 133)
      - Queen of Bermuda (2), 1933 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 133)
      - Pan America (7), [1928-1929] (Offsite-box 14, Folder 133)
    - Sailors' Snug Harbor, Staten Island (5), 1929, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 134)
    - Ships and shipping - miscellaneous (64), 1928, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 135)
  - Shoes
    Shoes is a small subseries focusing on shoes on display, the feet of those walking on the street, and one timely shot of a shoe that has just stepped in fresh, sticky chewing gum.
    - Shoes on display and stepping in gum (4), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 136)
      See also: Occupations - Shoe Shiners
  - Shops and Shopping
    Shops and Shopping includes views of a variety of mostly clothing and department stores as well as a number of photographs of fashionable window shoppers peering at displays and their own reflections in the windows. The Stroheim & Romann and Weber and Heilbroner stores are particularly well represented.
    - Bagoe, 86 Madison Ave. (drug store), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 137)
    - Bedolls, 34th St. and Sixth Ave. (2), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 137)
    - Bergdorf Goodman, 754 Fifth Ave., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 137)
    - Bloomingdale's, undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 137)
    - Broadstreet's, undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 137)
    - Curtis Furniture, undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 137)
    - Dennison's, 411 E. 32nd St. (2), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - De Pinna, 650 Fifth Ave., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - F.R. Tripler & Co., 366 Madison Ave., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - Featherly, Inc., Gowns, 19 East 61st St., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - Franklin Simon & Co., 414 Fifth Ave., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - Freess & Co., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - Gimbel Brothers, 1275 Broadway, undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - Joseph Hilton and Sons, Greeley Square, undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 138)
    - Kayser (4), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 139)
    - Lebolt & Co., Jewelers, 534 Fifth Ave., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 139)
    - Macy's [R.H. Macy & Co.], 34th St. and Broadway (3), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 139)
    - Mary Scott Rowland (2), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 140)
    - Richard Hudnut, 695 Fifth Ave., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 140)
    - S. H. Kress & Co. (3), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 140)
    - Sisto's Pharmacy, Polymol advertising in window, undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 140)
    - Stroheim & Romann, interiors and exteriors, 35 East 53rd Street and 515 Madison Ave. stores (13), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 141)
    - Walgreen Co., undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 142)
    - Weber and Heilbroner, includes photomontages (18), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 142)
    - Winkelman Shoe, 21 West 42nd St. (5), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 143)
    - Window shoppers, miscellaneous (32), undated (Offsite-box 15, Folder 144)
  - Skylines and Cityscapes
    Skylines and Cityscapes includes a variety of views of Manhattan from various vantage points, filed by Lower Manhattan skylines, Midtown Manhattan skylines, or skylines/rooftop views within Manhattan.
    - Lower Manhattan skylines (22), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 145)
    - Midtown Manhattan skylines (13), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 146)
    - Skylines, cityscapes, and rooftop views within Manhattan (31), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 147)
  - Sports and Recreation
    Sports and Recreation consists of a people engaging in a variety of leisure time activities. Most activities depicted are past times of wealthy Manhattanites, such as polo, tennis, and golf. A large series of photographs focuses on a group of young, well-dressed, wealthy New Yorkers traveling on a cruise aboard the Queen of Bermuda. A few spectator scenes and swimming and diving or beach scenes depict participants across a broader economic spectrum.
    - Amusement Parks, Coney Island (9), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 148)
    - Baseball (3), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 149)
    - Fencing (2), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 150)
    - Fishing (3), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 151)
    - Football (4), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 152)
    - Golf (11), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 153)
    - Horseback riding (5), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 154)
    - Model airplanes (4), undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 155)
    - Ocean travel, cruise aboard the Queen of Bermuda (26), [1932] (Offsite-box 17, Folder 156)
    - Polo (13), 1934, undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 157)
    - Shuffleboard (6), [1932], undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 158)
    - Skiing (2), undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 159)
    - Spectators (9), undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 160)
    - Swimming and diving [includes beach scenes] (21), undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 161)
    - Tennis (4), 1932, undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 162)
    - Track and field (2), undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 163)
  - Streets and Avenues
    Streets and Avenues consists of views of New York Streets in a variety of neighborhoods, from the signs and theaters of Broadway to shops along Fifth Avenue to the streets of Harlem. Streets and Avenue views are arranged into the follow subdivisions: Named Streets and Avenues, Numbered Avenues, and Numbered Streets; thereunder they are arranged alphabetically or numerically accordingly.
    - Named Streets and Avenues
      - Beaver and New Sts., undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 164)
      - Broadway and Wall Sts., including New York Stock Exchange, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 164)
      - Broadway, from Bowling Green, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 165)
      - Broadway and Exchange Place, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 165)
      - Broadway and 31st St., undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 165)
      - Broadway from 40th to 49th St. (13), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 166)
      - Broadway from 51st through 59th St. (2), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 167)
      - Broadway at 174th St., undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 167)
      - Broadway, unidentified cross streets (5), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 167)
      - Central Park South (2), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 168)
      - Central Park West at 62nd St., undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 168)
      - Chatham Square, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 168)
      - Forsyth St. near Grand St., undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 169)
      - Lexington Ave. from 42nd through 45th St. (3), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 169)
      - Madison Ave. at 28th St., undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 170)
      - Park Ave. from 20th through 59th St. (5), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 171)
      - Riverside Drive (2), 1925, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 172)
      - South St. (14), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 173)
      - Wall St. (4), [1926], undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 174)
      - Washington Mews (4), 1924, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 175)
      - Washington Square North (3), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 176)
    - Numbered Avenues
      - Second Ave., with view of the Chrysler Building in distance, [after 1929] (Offsite-box 18, Folder 177)
      - Third Ave. at 43rd St., with view of elevated railroad, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 178)
      - Third Ave., brownstones, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 178)
      - Fourth Ave., 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 179)
      - Fifth Ave., 34th to 36th Sts. (4), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 180)
      - Fifth Ave., 40th to 49th Sts., including aerial views (19), undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 181)
      - Fifth Ave., 57th to 60th Sts. (7), 1924, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 182)
      - Fifth Ave., unidentified, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 183)
      - Sixth Ave., 32nd through 46th Sts. and unidentified (9), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 184)
      - Eighth Ave. at 37th St., undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 185)
    - Numbered Streets
      - 14th St. at Union Square West (2), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 186)
      - 23rd through 26th Sts. (7), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 187)
      - 30th through 34th Sts. (12), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 188)
      - 40th St. (2), [1922] undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 189)
      - 42nd St. (13), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 190)
      - 43rd through 46th Sts. (4), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 191)
      - 47th through 49th Sts. (12), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 192)
      - 50th through 54th Sts. (17), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 193)
      - 57th through 58th Sts. (12), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 194)
      - West 66th St., no 69, undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 195)
      - East 73rd St., no. 301, undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 195)
      - East 86th St., undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 195)
      - East 96th St., undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 195)
      - West 130th St., no. 101, undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 195)
      - Unidentified street scenes (34), undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 196)
  - Television and Radio
    Television and Radio consists of photographs of microphones, equipment, studios and broadcasters from the early days of radio and television.
    - Microphones, NBC and unidentified, undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 197)
    - Radio Broadcasting -- CBS Radio studio, equipment and operators (3), undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 198)
    - Radio Broadcasting -- Crowd listening to election returns broadcast, undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 198)
    - Radio Broadcasting -- Radio studio scene, male pianist and female singer (3), undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 198)
    - Radio Broadcasting -- Radio photomontages (2), undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 198)
    - Radio Broadcasting -- WHN Radio, female broadcaster with dog (2), undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 198)